whalewisdom.com 2018-09-07

# user privacy policy

### Information Collection and Use

WhaleWisdom.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. To access certain features of the site we require you to register and create an account. Information collected from registering includes your name and email address. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to use our email alerts feature then your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. 

If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

### Email Alert Opt-Out Policy

Your contact information may be used to provide you with certain features of WhaleWisdom.com such as automated email alerts for new SEC filings. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. WhaleWisdom.com may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Service. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### How we may contact you

WhaleWisdom.com may send you information related to your account or services. Because we believe such information is important, you will not be given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

### Updating your information

You can terminate your account at any time, by sending an email to [admin@whalewisdom.com](mailto:admin@whalewisdom.com) requesting your account be deleted. We typically deactivate accounts within two business days of such requests. You should be aware, however, that residual copies of information may remain stored on our systems even after the deletion of information or the termination of your account 

### Security

WhaleWisdom.com is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. 

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

WhaleWisdom.com services and data utilize Amazon Elastic Cloud Compute (Amazon EC2) servers and Amazon Simple Email Services (SES). Both these services have a robust security policy. More information regarding Amazon EC2 and Amazon SES security and privacy policies can be found at <http://aws.amazon.com/ec2/> and <http://aws.amazon.com/ses/>, respectively. 

### Third-Party Online Advertising

We may use third parties who collect Information about Site Visitors through their own cookies, web beacons, and other technologies regarding your online activities, either on our Sites and/or other websites across the Internet, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties include advertisers and ad networks that may collect information about when you view or interact with one of their advertisements and may collect information regarding your activities on our Sites and your online activities over time and across different Websites. Like most advertisers, we place advertisements where we think they will be most relevant to the recipient. One way we do so is by allowing the advertising networks with whom we work to place their own cookies when an individual visits our Sites. This enables the network advertising company to recognize individuals who have previously visited our Sites. When the individual visits a third-party website on which that network advertising company has purchased ad space, the advertising company can then recognize the individual's interest in WhaleWisdom and deliver one of our advertisements. 

You may generally opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from certain third-party advertisers and ad networks. To learn more about these advertisements or to opt out, please visit the websites of the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) and the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/). 

### How do we manage data on children

In compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), this Site is not directed at children under the age of 13 and we do not intend to collect any personal identifiable information, such as name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, or social security number, from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with your personal identifiable information.

If you are under the age of 16 (EU & elsewhere), please ask your parent/guardian for their consent before submitting your personal information to this site.

If you have any reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 or 16 has provided us with his or her personal identifiable information, please contact us immediately for removal of that information from our databases. 

### Privacy Notice for EEA Individuals

This section covers disclosures on the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for users residing within EEA only. GDPR replaces the existing Directive 95/46/ec, and aims at harmonizing data protection laws in the EU that are fit for purpose in the digital age. The primary objective of the GDPR is to give citizens back control of their personal data. Please follow the link below to access WhaleWisdom's General Data Protection Notice. https://whalewisdom.com/info/gdpr_notice
